Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Yue'er
يوير
Soon will be my coronation ceremony
سوف يكون حفل تتويجي قريبا
And your auspicious time to wed in Mo City
ووقتك الميمون للزواج في مدينة مو
I promise you, sister
أعدك يا ​​أختي
It won't be long
لن يمضي وقت طويل
I'll make us siblings
سأجعلنا أشقاء
the most powerful people in the world
أقوى الأشخاص في العالم
Yes
نعم
Today is truly a blessed day
اليوم هو يوم مبارك حقا
Seems you came well prepared
يبدو أنك أتيت مستعدًا جيدًا
You ungrateful child
يا لك من طفل جاحد
You don't deserve the Nan name
أنت لا تستحق اسم نان
Today I'll punish you for the old Lord
اليوم سأعاقبك على الرب القديم
Huo Jingyun
هوو جينغيون
Didn't I already turn you into The Corrupted?
ألم أحولك بالفعل إلى الفاسد؟
You died in battle over ten years ago
لقد مت في المعركة منذ أكثر من عشر سنوات
You were Huo Jingyue, the banished general
لقد كنت هيو جينغيو، الجنرال المنفي
Well then
حسنا إذن
Never thought Father planned so far ahead
لم أكن أعتقد أن والدي خطط لهذا الأمر مسبقًا
He was preparing for this all along
لقد كان يستعد لهذا طوال الوقت
If that's the case
إذا كان الأمر كذلك
Then today I'll wipe you all out
ثم اليوم سأمسحكم جميعا
To end all future threats
لإنهاء جميع التهديدات المستقبلية
We've mastered the sachet formula
لقد أتقنا صيغة الكيس
All soldiers wear them now
كل الجنود يرتدونها الآن
We're no longer afraid of The Corrupted
نحن لم نعد خائفين من الفاسدين
We vow to defend Xuan Cheng to the death
نحن نتعهد بالدفاع عن شوان تشنغ حتى الموت
Attack!
هجوم!
General Huo, are you alright?
الجنرال هيو هل أنت بخير؟
Don't worry, I can handle it
لا تقلق، أنا قادر على التعامل مع الأمر
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Grandmaster, what are you doing?
سيدي الرئيس، ماذا تفعل؟
Grandmaster
الأستاذ الكبير
Look closely
انظر عن كثب
See who I really am
انظر من أنا حقًا
Dong Qing
دونغ تشينغ
You're lucky to be alive
أنت محظوظ لأنك على قيد الحياة
Yue'er
يوير
Are you really leaving me behind?
هل حقا تتركني خلفك؟
Brother
أخ
I...
أنا...
Nan Zhengci
نان زينجسي
You're a monster in human skin, unforgivable
أنت وحش في جلد إنسان، لا يغتفر
Today is the day you die
اليوم هو يوم موتك
Brother
أخ
Brother—Yue'er
الأخ—يوير
Stop fighting
اوقف القتال
Surrender
يستسلم
Master Dong Qing
المعلم دونغ تشينغ
Please spare my second brother
أرجوك أن تنقذ أخي الثاني
I'll persuade him to change
سأقنعه بالتغيير
No way
مستحيل
I'm not wrong
انا لست مخطئا
They're the ones at fault
إنهم هم المخطئون
They all deserve to die
كلهم يستحقون الموت
Die without regret
مت بلا ندم
Today I'll rid the world of you
اليوم سأخلص العالم منك
And bring peace to Xuan Cheng
وأحضر السلام إلى شوان تشنغ
Darn it
اللعنة عليك
He's going to put the Broodmother inside himself
إنه سيضع الأم الحاضنة بداخله
Winner is king, loser is outlaw
الفائز هو الملك والخاسر هو الخارج عن القانون
I, Nan Zhengci, will die fighting
أنا، نان تشنغشي، سأموت في القتال
Never as a coward
لا تكن جبانًا أبدًا
Only by stabbing his Vital Core
فقط عن طريق طعن قلبه الحيوي
can he be truly destroyed
هل يمكن تدميره حقا؟
Huo—General Huo
هوو - الجنرال هوو
Quick, hurry, get up!
سريعًا، أسرع، استيقظ!
Stab his Vital Core with the blade
اطعن قلبه الحيوي بالشفرة
Hurry, can't hold on much longer
اسرع، لا يمكنني الصمود لفترة أطول
Yue'er
يوير
Why?
لماذا؟
Brother
أخ
I'm not just your sister
أنا لست أختك فقط
I'm also Xuan Cheng's princess
أنا أيضًا أميرة شوان تشنغ
I must choose
يجب علي أن أختار
to let Xuan Cheng's people survive
للسماح لشعب شوان تشنغ بالبقاء على قيد الحياة
Strange
غريب
Why does the Broodmother fear ordinary blades?
لماذا تخاف الأم الشفرات العادية؟
This blade is smeared with my brother's blood
هذا النصل ملطخ بدماء أخي
His blood can counter all poisons
دمه قادر على مقاومة كل السموم
Brother
أخ
You've suffered too much
لقد عانيت كثيرا
Rest now
استرح الآن
Yue—Yue'er
يو-يوير
Brother
أخ
So beautiful
جميلة جدا
Didn't expect to see today's sun
لم أتوقع رؤية شمس اليوم
If only Master and Luobo were here
لو كان السيد ولوبو هنا
They've never truly left
إنهم لم يغادروا أبدًا حقًا
You have Master's tiger tooth
لديك سن النمر للماجستير
And Luobo's Soulcleaver
و Soulcleaver لـ Luobo
They've always been with you
لقد كانوا معك دائما
Protecting you
حمايتك
Have you decided?
هل قررت؟
You truly won't stay to inherit Xuan Cheng's lordship?
هل أنت حقًا لن تبقى لترث سيادة Xuan Cheng؟
To benefit Xuan Cheng's people
لصالح شعب شوان تشنغ
After the battle with The Corrupted
بعد المعركة مع الفاسدين
I firmly believe
أنا أؤمن بشدة
Princess Yue will surely become
الأميرة يوي سوف تصبح بالتأكيد
a diligent and caring ruler
حاكم مجتهد ومهتم
As for me
أما بالنسبة لي
I grew up in Cloudveil Temple
لقد نشأت في معبد كلاودفيل
I've always wanted to see the world
لقد أردت دائمًا رؤية العالم
Just as Master said
كما قال المعلم
Uphold justice, slay evil
إحقاق العدل، وقتل الشر
Brother Dong Qing
الأخ دونغ تشينغ
Sister
أخت
I want to be like you too
أريد أن أكون مثلك أيضًا
Uphold justice, roam the world with my sword
أدافع عن العدالة، وأجوب العالم بسيفى
Well...
حسنًا...
I think
أظن
Master Dong Qing dislikes us two poison masters
السيد دونغ تشينغ يكرهنا نحن السادة السم
Doesn't want us to help rid evil
لا يريد منا أن نساعد في التخلص من الشر
No, no, that's not it
لا، لا، ليس هذا هو الأمر
I'm just afraid
أنا خائف فقط
you'd truly want to come with me
كنت تريد حقا أن تأتي معي
I do
أفعل
And you?
وأنت؟
Let's go
دعنا نذهب
Let's go, Brother Dong Qing
دعنا نذهب، الأخ دونغ تشينغ
Watch your step
انتبه لخطواتك